dealfish.com.ng 2012-05-10

# Privacy policy (UPDATED) • Dealfish.com.ng

  * » Privacy policy (UPDATED)

#### Privacy policy

Dealfish, a division of Media 24 Nigeria Limited, registration number RC 613319, a company incorporated in accordance with the laws of Nigeria, (hereinafter referred to as **“we”** or **“us”** or **“our”** ) is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected at all times when using our website- www.dealfish.com.ng (the **“Site”** ) and the temporary classified advertising services we offer via the Site (hereinafter referred to as **“the Services”** ). 

This Privacy Policy governs the use of the information we collect about you. 

  1. We reserve the right to contact and send information to users of our Site ( **“the Users”** ), including you, using the contact details (including email address and mobile phone number) provided to us during your registration. In this regard you undertake to ensure that such details are up to date and to inform us of any change in your contact details. We will not be liable for information being sent to out-of-date contact details. 
  2. **Children below 18 years of age should not access the Site or use the Services.** We do not have any intention of collecting any personally identifiable information from individuals under 18 years of age. If you are aware that a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, please contact us and we will remove the information. 
  3. The security of the information that you provide to us is important to us. To prevent unauthorized disclosure, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have in place reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure any information we collect online. 
  4. **It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer.** When using a shared computer, be sure to sign off and do not opt to stay logged in to the Site. Should you realize that you accidentally allowed a third party to access your account, you must let us know immediately, as you may be held liable for their actions in your name. 
  5. We do not have any control over the privacy practices of any external websites linked to our Site and will not be liable for the content of such websites or use of information provided to them. 
  6. Other Users who advertise on the Site may collect certain information that is available to them through your interaction with their advertisements ( **“Ads”** ). We have no control or knowledge as to their practices and it is suggested that you read their privacy policy separately before clicking on any Ads. 
  7. You agree that we may electronically collect, store and use the following of your personal information: 
    1. email address 
    2. mobile phone number
    3. closest city 
    4. non-personal browsing habits and click patterns
    5. IP address 
  8. We collect, store and use the abovementioned information for the following purposes: 
    1. to greet you when you access the Site; 
    2. to inform you of facts relating to your access and use of the Site and/or the Service; 
    3. to inform you about competitions and special offers from us and/or our partners and/or affiliates; 
    4. to compile non-personal statistical information about your browsing habits, click-patterns and access to the Site; 
    5. to verify your identity when transacting with us or with other Users on the Site; 
    6. to furnish information to you and other Users regarding transactions, potential transactions and subscriptions. 
  9. The information detailed above is collected either electronically by using cookies or is provided voluntarily by you. You may determine cookie use independently through your browser settings. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features that recognize your account as logged on and other Site features. Further, to help us tailor the Site to the needs and interests of our Users, or for other purposes, we may gather aggregate, permanently non-personally identifiable information via cookies. Examples include the type of Internet browser our Users are using, the frequency of visits to our Site and which pages our Users viewed. We may share these aggregate statistics with others. The use of cookies is standard on the internet and many major web sites use them. 
  10. We may collect, maintain, save, compile and share any permanently de-identified information collected from you, subject to the following provisions: 
    1. We shall not disclose your personal information to anyone other than our partners and affiliates, unless you consent thereto; 
    2. We shall disclose information without your consent only where required to do so by law or any regulatory authority or where necessary to enforce our rights under this Privacy Policy or the dealfish [Terms & Conditions](http://dealfish.com.ng/rules/); 
    3. We may compile, use, share and otherwise process any permanently de-identified information that does not relate and cannot be traced back to any specific individual. 
  11. We own and retain all rights to non-personal statistical information collected and compiled by us. 
  12. **Please note that any personal information you decide to include within the content of your Ads is not protected by this Privacy Policy.** In accordance with the dealfish [Terms & Conditions](http://dealfish.com.ng/rules/), by submitting Ads you are agreeing to them being published on the Site as well as in other print and/or electronic media (be it another online classifieds site, or newspaper or otherwise) and any personal information you decide to include within your Ads (such as your name, phone number or address etc) will consequently also be made public. **We will not be held liable in any way in relation to the information so disclosed by you in your Ads.**
  13. By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this Privacy Policy. If we change our Privacy Policy we will post the changes on this webpage on the Site so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. Upon change of our Privacy Policy, your continued use of the Site and/or Services will signify that you agree to such change(s). 
  14. Note that if we should sell, transfer or close our business, or undergo a merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganisation or liquidation, then we shall be entitled to transfer, sell or assign any or all information collected via the Site (including your personal information) to one or more relevant third parties, to be used by them in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy
